UNITE Research Department Chronological Correspondence Files 6000/014
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Research Department Chronological Correspondence Files
1995- 1997
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
6000/014
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Records.
This collection includes records of the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union of America.
6766416
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 29, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000 AV: UNITE Audio-Visual Collection 6000 G: UNITE Posters 6000 MB: UNITE Memorabilia 6000 P: UNITE Photographs 6000/003: UNITE Research Department Historic Files 6000/020: UNITE Research Department Files 6000/020 P: UNITE Research Department Photographs
Textile workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees. Research Dept.--Archives; UNITE HERE (Organization) -- Archives
6766416
- CHRON File July, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  All folders contain CHRON Files
- August, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- October, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- November, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- December, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- November, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- January, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- December, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- January, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- February, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- March, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- April, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- May, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- June, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- July, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- August, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- September, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- October, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- November, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- December, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- January/February, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- March/April, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)